Anagha Inamdar

Actively seeking Summer 2017 internship opportunities.

New York, NY - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Anagha-Inamdar/546a95d552742442

I am Anagha Inamdar, currently pursuing my Masters Degree in Information Systems from Pace University. My concentration is 'Database Management and Technologies'. I have completed my first semester with a GPA of 3.8 on 4, with subjects

- -Database Management Systems
- -Project and Change Management
- -Business Telecommunication.

I am currently pursuing 'Database Programming', 'Big Data' and 'Data Warehousing and mining' for my second semester.

I have been continuously working on MySQL, PHP, Hadoop, HDFS, Tableau, RapidMiner.

I have worked at 'Accenture' for a period of 22 months on SAP Technology. I have worked on functional modules such as SAP-MM. Technical modules such as SAP-ABAP and also SAP-ISU.

I am also familiar with C, C++, Java, HTML, CSS, PHP.

I have worked on softwares such as MS-Office, Photoshop, Eclipse, MATLAB, LabVIEW.

I am open to opportunities which will allow me to use my versatile skills and which gives me a platform to learn new technologies.

I would always welcome an informational chat about any possible opportunity that is suited to my skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Accenture - Mumbai, India - August 2014 to June 2016

Software Engineer March 2016 - June 2016

- •Enhanced the SAP legacy system for client from the requirement to the deployment phase as the SAP-ISU consultant.
- •Analyzed and regulated the configuration of the system for successful implementation of the product, developed new RATES (codes), created test cases according to the required criteria, implemented the test cases end to end and successfully documented the entire process.
- •Mentored junior resources, imparted knowledge transfer and guided them during the testing phase.

Associate Software Engineer October 2014 - July 2015

- •Performed the dual role of Data Migration Consultant along with the role of a SAP-MM consultant.
- •Extracted data provided by client from the original system and formatted it according to the requirements of the new systems.
- •Remodelled LSMW (Legacy System Migration Workbench), a tool in SAP, for easy loading of vast amounts of complex data in the system.
- •Performed post validation of output data by generating SQVI queries in SAP to extract the data.
- •Utilized Excel extensively for data formatting and post-load data validation.
- •Worked on the procurement cycle and individually handled creation of Purchase Requests and Purchase Orders to make the further workflow easier.

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information Systems

Pace University, Seidenberg School of CSIS - New York, NY September 2016 to May 2018

Bachelor of Engineering in Instrumentation

Mumbai University - Mumbai, Maharashtra September 2010 to May 2014

SKILLS

Microsoft Office (6 years), SAP (2 years), C++ (1 year), C (1 year), Java (2 years), Eclipse (1 year), HTML 5 (2 years), MySQL (3 years), Change Management (Less than 1 year)

LINKS

http://www.linkedin.com/in/anagha-inamdar

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Voluntary Leadership Roles-

1) Accenture, Mumbai, India August 2014 - June 2016

GPTW (Great Place to Work) Committee

- •Collaborated with a team to organize an large scale employee event for the Mumbai office.
- 2) VESIT- International Society of Automation Student Chapter July 2012 June 2014 Event Organizer (July 2013-June 2014) | Junior Editor (July 2012 June 2013)
- •Coordinated and organized various events which included technical paper presentations, robotics events, and educational workshops
- •Collaborated with a team of students to work on monthly publication of ISA magazine as well as an e-magazine.